Wrege, Charles D. Research Photographs 6395 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles D. Wrege Research Photographs
1902-2007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Wrege, Charles D.
6395 P
1.11 cubic feet
1.11 linear ft.
Photographs.
8691869
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 25, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Charles "Chuck" Wrege finished his undergraduate degree in Upsala College, obtained his Masters degree at the New School fo Social Research and another Masters of Business Administration and his Ph.D. at NYU. He taught industrial management at Rutgers University for 30 years. He became a renowned historian, researcher and writer. He is regarded as a "National Treasure" by many in his field because of his expertise and the seminal research he has done in the area of management history.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8691869
- Spring Trip - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- E-901 Relay Assembly (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hawthorne Works (Box 1, Folder 3)
- J + F (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sea Venture to Bermuda - 6/3-10/1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Pictures of a home interior (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Misc. slides (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Greenwood (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Feiss; Tarbell; Kepple (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Color slides of Hawthorne Works (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Nov. 1967-Dec. 1967 - Dukes Farm (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Pyott Foundry Co. - negative/slide sheets (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Western Electric Photos: 149583 - Perforator; 149585 - Reproduction -- Test Room - 1927 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Transparencies - Hawthorne Works 1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Boxly Photos (1978) -- 4x5 negatives and prints of "Boxly" for Jack Robin 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Misc. color prints (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Various photos of Street Cars - New Jersey; Atlantic City (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Midvale (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Negatives of car 4001 of Chicago - Surface Lines 1934 (some photos) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Daniel Drawbaugh - photo negative (1965) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hawthorne Photos (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Street Car Pictures, negatives, Post card (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Time - Trek! (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Negatives of woman working in a machine shop (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Misc. - Negs.; Post card; Street Car photo (Box 1, Folder 26)
- B. Millish 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Pictures of Houses (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Women working in a factory (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Pyott Foundary Co. (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Midvale Photo from Howard Myers, Jr. (George Eyre Smith, circa 1940) (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Picture of a factory (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Mr. Gilbreth -- Photos and negatives (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Virginia Feiss Photo (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Photo of two men (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Dwight Merritt Photo (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Utopia Designer Jeans - The Oracle for Tempomatic (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Tacony Edge. Tools and Hammer Factory Pictures (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Pennock + Stoll Photos (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Better Lighting Photo 1925 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Photographs of Gilbreth Surgery Photos 3/31/1980 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Car 1728 Kinney Line - Circa 1915 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Clockwork post card; No. 9000 street car photo; Fiche - (NY (St) Leg Assembly) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Photos of Setting Stories in "Presbyterian Burying Ground", Middletown, NY (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photos - August 6, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Photo copies of photos
- Richard Feiss - Ida Tarbell, Seebohm Roundtree (Box 2, Folder 3)
- C.D. Wrege Photo - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Photos of C.D. Wrege at School of Business, Rutger Univ. - 1988 [9/28/1988] (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Holland Submarine off Elizabeth, N.Y. Photos (Box 2, Folder 6)
- "Mac" Photo with wife - June 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Photos of C. Wrege 1962 + B. Wrege 1952, 1952-1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Photo of Alexander Hamilton at West Point on the Hudson, NY - 1940 (Hudson River Boat) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Frederick W. Taylor examining concrete - 1914 (original photo) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Midvale Photos - (photo copies of photos) -- pulled from 6013 P (Box 2, Folder 11)
- "Boxly" - 2007 (Photo copies of photos) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Hawthorne (Photo copies of photos) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous loose photos (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Taylor slides (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Frank Gilbreth (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Hawthorne Works - 1902-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  oversize photograph